[
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "hakkinda",
		"antwort": "bezüglich; um",
		"phase": 1,
		"naechsteabfrage": "24.03.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "esmer",
		"antwort": "dunkelhaarig",
		"phase": 2,
		"naechsteabfrage": "24.03.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "sarışın",
		"antwort": "blond",
		"phase": 1,
		"naechsteabfrage": "24.03.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "kumral",
		"antwort": "dunkelblond; hellbraun",
		"phase": 2,
		"naechsteabfrage": "10.04.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "kızıl",
		"antwort": "rot",
		"phase": 2,
		"naechsteabfrage": "08.04.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "sakal",
		"antwort": "Bart",
		"phase": 4,
		"naechsteabfrage": "26.05.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "bıyık",
		"antwort": "Schnurbart",
		"phase": 2,
		"naechsteabfrage": "10.04.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "peygamber",
		"antwort": "Prophet",
		"phase": 1,
		"naechsteabfrage": "24.03.2023"
	},
	{
		"thema": "Türkisch",
		"frage": "boylu",
		"antwort": "Größe",
		"phase": 1,
		"naechsteabfrage": "24.03.2023"
	}
]